# **RAUL A. SURIA JR**

Blk e 6 lot 6 Brgy San Lorenzo ruiz 1 Dasmariñas City, Cavite 09951091861

stadnitzki.nero.nero@gmail.com



# **SUMMARY:**

I am a graduate of a 2 year course in Computer Technology with almost 2 years of work experience in BPO. I am very good in critical thinking, analysis, problem solving and communication. Looking for a new opportunity in web development to strive for growth and learning.

# **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

**COLLEGE** June 2013 – Feb 2015

Associate in Computer Technology

Asian Institute of Science and Technology

**HIGHSCHOOL** June 2011 – March 2012

Dasmarinas National Highschool

**ELEMENTARY** June 2006 – March 2007

Dasmarinas Bagong Bayan Elementary School

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

National certificate 2 passer computer hardware servicing

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- PHP
- MySQL
- Bootstrap
- Laravel
- Node JS

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Customer Service Representative / Real time analyst (WFM), WNS global services, 9th floor 1880 building Eastwood City Libis, Quezon City September 2015 – August 2017

- Providing good customer experience
- Educating the customer about the airline policies and products
- Providing resolutions for all inquiries.
- Forecasting if an interval will fail or not
- Reporting details about the productivity of the account
- Managing agents on their breaks

# Technician, MAXSAVER/ Mila De lin Trading, Dasmarinas city, Cavite January 2015 – February 2015 (On the job training)

- Installing computer hardware and software systems
- Maintaining computer parts and performance
- Troubleshooting of computer issues
- Setting up computer security measures
- Configuring computer networks and offering technical support.
- Customer service operations

# **PERSONAL DATA**

Height : 5'4
Weight : 53 lbs.
Status : Single

Religion : Iglesia ni Cristo Birthdate : April 8, 1995

Gender : Male
Nationality : Filipino

Language Spoken : English, Tagalog

# **CHARACTER REFRERENCE**

NAME	DESIGNATION	<b>CONTACT NUMBER</b>
Joey Alabin	Agent	09082128366
Pauleen Aunario	Programmer	09267970031
Nikko Brylle Ramos	Manager	09295975431
I hereby certify that the above information are true and correct		
		Signature